[
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Most reliable car company in the world ?",
        "correct": "Toyota",
        "incorrect": ["Hyundai", "Kia", "Suzuki"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which is India's first car?",
        "correct": "Hindustan Ambassador",
        "incorrect": ["Premier padmini", "Maruti 800", "Zen"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the best-selling car of all time??",
        "correct": "Toyota Corolla",
        "incorrect": ["Suzuki swift", "Baleno", "Innova"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What was the name of the first car sent into space?",
        "correct": "The Tesla Roadster",
        "incorrect": [
            "Mercedes Benz",
            "BMW",
            "Volvo"
        ]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is the smallest car ever made?",
        "correct": "Peel p50",
        "incorrect": ["Renault Kwid", "Honda Brio", "Tata Nano"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "How many rings does the Audi logo have?",
        "correct": "4",
        "incorrect": ["3", "5", "6"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which country is the largest car producer in the world? ",
        "correct": "China",
        "incorrect": ["Japan", "India", "Portuguese"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": " A bull is part of the logo for which Italian luxury car company??",
        "correct": "Lamborghini",
        "incorrect": ["Peugeot", "porshe", "ferrari"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which car company first introduced seat belts as a standard feature?",
        "correct": "Volvo",
        "incorrect": ["BMW", "Tesla", "Toyota"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which company owns Rolls Royce?",
        "correct": "BMW",
        "incorrect": ["Audi", "Mercedes", "Range Rover"]
    }
]